zanru.com 2014-06-25

# Zanru - Privacy Policy

We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Yapzo Media respects each site visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website. For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, to notify visitors about updates to our Web site and it is never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

You do not need to register in order to enter our site. However, subscription to certain services may require a user to complete a registration form. During registration a user must give certain contact information, but we never sell or give away this information. It is only gathered to contact the user about services on our site for which s/he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (income level, gender, etc.), and unique identifiers (username, password, etc.). Giving additional information helps provide a more personalized experience on our site, but is not required. We publish a newsletter, and we never sell or share our subscribers' email or mailing addresses. We operate online surveys, and we never sell or share our subscribers' email addresses. We do show advertisement to our users, which is handled by Google Adsense or similar services. So any such concerns with our advertising, should be directed to them respectedly.

Furthermore:

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. We are in no way responsible for notifying users when such changes occur.

We are committed to resolving disputes as quickly as possible. If problems arise, users may contact via our contact form.

[Zanru.com](http://zanru.com/) uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. **If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to:<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.**

If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via our contact page.
